JOHN HERALD SANDOY

Dasmariñas, Cavite 4114 | 09755949265 | sandoyherald@gmail.com

SUMMARY

Committed professional offering more than 6 years of experience in the field of web application development. Excellent communication skills and a consistent team player in all sorts of environments. Seeking to expand talents by bringing a wealth of expertise to a well-established company.

EXPERIENCE

09/2020 to Current

WordPress Developer

Cornerstone Digital Australia - New South Wales, Australia

- Organised WordPress training and guidance to provide clients with hands-on experience.
- Generated WordPress themes enable change of layout and provide design choices for website.
- Actively listened to customers to fully understand requests and address concerns.
- Translating Design to Actual WordPress Site

02/2018 to 03/2021

Frontend Developer

GarageFarm.NET - Steyning, , West Sussex United Kingdom

- Designed and implemented website interface for mobile, desktop and tablets.
- Contributed to back-end experience and collaborated on APIs.
- Built reusable code to utilise for other projects and to minimise costs.
- Handled special projects designated by senior developer.

01/2017 to 02/2018

Web Developer

Xtendly - Muntinlupa, Alabang

- Handled special projects designated by senior developer.
- Built reusable code to utilise for other projects and to minimise costs.
- Translating PSD Designs into Wordpress Pages
- Created backup files on servers and directories to avoid data loss.
- Collaborated with designers to implement concept and design of website.
- Troubleshot website on different browsers to determine quality.

08/2016 to 12/2016

Frontend Developer

Group 11 - Las Pinas, Philippines

- Designed and implemented website interface for mobile, desktop and tablets.
- Built reusable code to utilise for other projects and to minimise costs.
- Responded to queries on private messages or comments to address issues and resolve complaints.

SKILLS

- Website Optimisation
- HTML Coding
- Javascript
- Jquery
- Content Management System
- GIT
- Wordpress
- CSS
- Full-Stack Development
- Adobe Photoshop

(CMS) Platforms

EDUCATION

2016 Bachelor of Science: Information Technology

STI College Dasmarinas - Dasmarinas

2011 Associate's Degree: Web Application Development

ACLC College - Las Pinas

CERTIFICATIONS

• Successfully completing the intensive I.T Coding Bootcamp of Zuitt Learning Institute Incorporated.

COMPLETION OF BOOTCAMP TRAINING AT ZUITT

Certifies the completion of all the prescribed requirements of Zuitt's
Developer Course using GIT, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Javascript, MongoDB,
NodeJS, ExpressJS, and ReactJS, as well as Full-stack Web Development.